ARINZE PETER CHINEDU

PYTHON DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am an adaptable professional developer with 4+ years of experience and a proven knowledge in blending art of design with skill of programming, real time data, and web design to deliver engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software development role in your company.

EDUCATION

January 2015 - September 2019. Nnamdi Azikiwe University. Awka, Nigeria.

Bachelor of Science, computer Science. Honors: cum laude (GPA: 4.5/5.0).

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Python
- Diango
- MySQL
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
 - ❖ React
 ❖ Ui/Ux
- Photoshop
- ❖ Git & Github
 - Heroku
 - AWS

CONTACT

Phone: (+234) 903-280-6278

Skype: https://join.skype.com/invite/HfuVGUMZNaQm

Email: breezeconcept3@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/Mr-IRobot/

My Website: https://breezeconcept.com/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/breeze-s-concept-578a6b1b5

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

SEP 2019 – Present CEO BREEZE CONCEPT, AWKA, NIGERIA.

- Managed a small scale firm that offers services to businesses and individuals
- The services include; web development (android/iOS), software development, branding, Ui/Ux, video editing, photo editing/manipulation and photo arts.
- We help these businesses to scale up by providing an online presence for their products and services.

SEP 2019 – Present Frontend web developer Breeze concept, Awka, Nigeria.

- Developed landing pages, dashboards and online applications using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap and Javascript.
- Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quickloading sites with particular.

September 2021 - January 2022 Backend web developer KLIQ, Lagos, Nigeria.

 Developed an e-commerce website that uses data analytics to visualize the data on products available and showcases a statistical report on the data.

CERTIFICATION

September 2019

BSc in Computer science and programming

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

SOME WORK REFERENCE:

Portfolio website: www.johnchibuzz.com

Affiliate marketing website: www.kliqaffiliate.com

To see more of my works - Visit:

www.breezeconcept.com/projects